# Dorin Gimpel Gal

Proactive Team Member with 2 years of experience in special education. Committed to maintaining efficiency and excellent quality assurance. Skilled at working with no supervision.

A sharp individual with a team player attitude and well-honed skills in providing support and listening.

## Contact

## **Address**

Kiryat Biyalik

#### **Phone**

052 459 4611

#### E-mail

doringim1@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dorin-gimpel-gal-a3b3b019b/

## **Skills**

Figma	Excellent
Adobe illustrator	Excellent
Adobe photoshop	Very Good
Adobe XD	Very Good
Html	Very Good
CSS	Very Good
Microsoft office	Excellent

# **Work History**

**2023-09 - High school UI UX & graphic design teacher** Atid- Boarding Schools, Kiryat Bialik, Israel

2020-09 - Freelance graphic designer

2017-09 - Special Education Teacher2019-09 Elor - Boarding Schools , Hadera, Israel

# **Education**

2024-02 - Full Stack .Net Developer

Hacker U Academy - Ramat-Gan, Israel

2019-09 - UI UX Design Cours

2020-12 Netcraft Academy - Beni-Brak, Israel

2019-09 - B.Ed: Special Education Teacher and Math

**2020-12** Gordon College Of Education - Haifa, Israel